Register of the William Hallam Tuck papers, 1914-1957
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1914-1965, undated, (bulk 1940-1941). (Box 3-8)
  - Sweden, 4 January 1946 (Folder 7: 13)
    "Bread-grain supply"
  - Universitas, Ltd. records, 1940-1942 (Folder 7: 14)
    See also Oversize File Box 11 Folder 8
  - University of Louvain, 28 June 1927 (Folder 7: 15)
    Cinquième Centenaire de la Fondation de l'Université
  - University of Louvain, 1928 (Folder 7: 16)
    The Legend of the "Francs-Tireurs" of Louvain,
  - University of Louvain, circa 1920s (Folder 7: 17)
    List of Inscriptions on the Walls of the Library University of Louvain
  - University of Louvain, Pose et Bénédiction de la Première Pierre de la Nouvelle Bibliothèque, 28 July 1921 (Folder 7: 18)
  - Miscellany, circa 1941-1945 (Folder 8: 1)
- Memorabilia and Ephemera, 1915, 1919, 1944, undated (Box 8-9, 11)
  Arranged by title. See also Oversize File.
  - Collection de Douze Vues de Waterloo, undated (Folder 8: 2)
    Folio containing a map of the Battle of Waterloo and twelve lithographs of the surrounding landscape
  - Havelange École des Filles clothbound message book, 1 July 1915 (Folder 9)
  - Hoover Overseas and War Service Organizations Reunion Dinner program, 3 March 1929 (Folder 8: 3)
    Tuck is listed as a guest
  - "Message des enfants de France libérée aux enfants americains", 4 July 1944 (Folder 8: 4)
  - Postcards, undated (Folder 8: 5)
    French text and couplets
  - Reception honoring Ferdinand Foch invitation, 1919 December 13 (Folder 8: 6)
  - Soupe de Guerre, circa 1915 October (Folder 8: 7)
    Bound postcards including images of soup kitchens in Belgium.
  - United States Festival of Remembrance program, undated (Folder 8: 8)
- Photographs, circa 1915-1960 (Box 8-11)
  Includes a set of loose photographs and two albums featuring members from the Commission for Relief in Belgium members, circa 1915-1920. See also Oversize File.
  - Buildings, objects, military procession, circa 1935, undated (Folder 8: 9)
  - Group poses, meetings, circa 1915-1920, circa 1950-1960 (Folder 8: 10)
  - Album, circa 1916-1920 (Folder 9)
    Portrait of Tuck on page 44 of album
  - Album, circa 1916-1920 (Folder 10)
- Oversize File, circa 1916-1950, undated (Box 11)
  Includes oversize materials relating to Tuck's service with the United States Naval Reserve and collected reports and documents relating to his relief activities and interests.
  - Biographical File, 1945-1946 (Folder 11)
    - United States Naval Reserve Records, 1945-1946 (Folder 11: 1)
      Includes documents related to the Economics Division, organizational charts, and a rice chart
  - Subject File, 1914-1958 (Folder 11)
    - Belgian American Educational Foundation Inc. documents, 1938, 1945 (Folder 11: 2)
    - Collected Publications, 1914-1915, 1929, 1941, undated (Folder 11: 3)
    - Hoover, Herbert printed addresses, 1940, 1945, 1958 (Folder 11: 4)
    - Maps, circa 1916-1920, circa 1935-1950, undated. (Folder 11: 5)
    - National Committee for Food for the Small Democracies document, 1941 (Folder 11: 6)
      Document is a memorandum regarding the ration situation in Belgium and Central Poland
    - Poland related document, circa 1945 (Folder 11: 7)
      "Problems of Social Welfare in Poland", map included
    - Universitas, Ltd. record, 5 March 1941 (Folder 11: 8)
  - Memorabilia, circa 1916 (Folder 11)
    - Posters, circa 1916 (Folder 11: 9)
  - Photographs, circa 1950 (Folder 11)
    - Group portrait taken in New York, circa 1950 (Folder 11: 10)
      Herbert Hoover is seated to the far right